We're going to find out the gender of
baby number four. I'm so excited.
>> Baby number four. Baby number four.
>> Yesterday was my anatomy scan. I never
end up doing the early testing, so this
is when I find out. But of course, we
want to find out with our girl. So, we
did ask if she could put the gender in
an envelope. And I'm not going to lie, I
was so tempted for her to just tell me
right then and there. But baby looked
completely healthy, which is what
matters most.
>> What we're going to do is we're going to
run into Costco, get some flowers. I'm
going to make both a pink bouquet and a
blue bouquet. And then I think we're
going to have the girls surprise them.
What do you think about that?
>> good about it.
>> Now, I've never done a flower bouquet
gender reveal. But how hard could it be?
It definitely seemed easier and quicker
than doing a cake. But with the flowers
being in the back, the girls got to fill
up on their favorite samples, which is a
win for everyone because they were in
such a great mood.
>> Now, we actually have to find the
flowers.
>> We faded to the flowers.
>> And it took 2 seconds to find the girl
flowers. So, I was probably over
confident at this point.
>> see any blue, but there's like a deep
purple.
>> And this is when I realized this is why
people hire professionals. There was
quite literally zero blue flowers. And I
don't think I'm going to have time to go
to another store.
>> These are all the flowers we got so far.
>> realize finding blue flowers was going
to be as hard as it is, but we got some
purple and then some deep purple, which
is kind of like blue, so.
>> Now, we're going to go check out.
>> Come back for part two to find out if
we're having a baby girl or baby
Rapunzel.